Guide to the Henry Draper Image Collection MC.230
New York University Archives
- Series II. Henry Draper Moon Images, 1862, 1872, undated
  - 10-40 Second Exposure, 5 August 1872; cuid14872 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 10 Second Exposure, 18 August 1872; cuid14873 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Last Quarter Moon, 24 August 1872; cuid14550; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14551; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14552; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14553; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14554; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14555; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14556; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Moon Image Taken with 28" Telescope, 1872; cuid14557; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Moon, circa late 19th century; cuid14558; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Moon, circa late 19th century; cuid14889; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Moon, circa late 19th century; cuid14892; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Series III. Glass Plate Negative Fragments, 1877-1910
  - Spectra, 3 April 1877; cuid14832; Glass plate fragments (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Solar Spectrum?, 26 March 1879; cuid14864; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Founders Monument, circa 1900; cuid14817; Glass plate fragments (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Draper's Physical Laboratory Behind His Wooster Street Home, NYC, undated; cuid14810; Glass plate fragments (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Draper's New York Home or Naval Observatory in Washington, DC, undated; cuid14834; Glass plate fragments (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14811; Glass plate fragments (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14812; Glass plate fragments (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14813; Glass plate fragments (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14814; Glass plate fragments (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14815; Glass plate fragments (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14816; Glass plate fragments (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14818; Glass plate fragments (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14819; Glass plate fragments (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14820; Glass plate fragments (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14821; Glass plate fragments (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14822; Glass plate fragments (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14823; Glass plate fragments (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14824; Glass plate fragments (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14825; Glass plate fragments (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14826; Glass plate fragments (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14827; Glass plate fragments (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14828; Glass plate fragments (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14829; Glass plate fragments (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14830; Glass plate fragments (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14831; Glass plate fragments (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14833; Glass plate fragments (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14835; Glass plate fragments (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14836; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14837; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14838; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14839; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14840; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14841; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14842; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14843; Glass plate fragments (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14844; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14845; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14846; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14847; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14848; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14849; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14850; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14851; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Segments of Solar Disk, undated; cuid14852; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fragment (Mended), undated; cuid14853; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14854; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14855; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14856; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Distribution of Stars of Type M, undated; cuid14857; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14858; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14899; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14859; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14860; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14861; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14900; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14901; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14862; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14863; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Solar Spectrum?, undated; cuid14865; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Box of Fragments, undated; cuid14866; Glass plate fragments (Box 26)
- Series IV. Henry Draper-Related Observatories and Laboratories Images, 1896-1898, undated
  - Draper Domes at Harvard College Observatory, circa 1896; cuid14559; Glass plate and negative (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Draper's Clark Refractor Installed at Harvard College, circa 1896; cuid14563; Negative (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Draper Domes and Telescope, View from South of Observatory at Harvard College, 1897; cuid14875 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Lantern slide, broken.
  - 8" Draper Camera at the Harvard College Observatory, circa 1898; cuid14562; Negative (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Naval Observatory, undated; cuid14560; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Naval Observatory, undated; cuid14561; Glass plate (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Draper's Laboratory, undated; cuid14565; Glass plate (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Draper's Laboratory, undated; cuid14566; Photographic print, copy of image (1) in this box. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Draper's Laboratory Equipment, undated; cuid14567; Glass plate (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Draper's Laboratory Equipment, undated; cuid14568; Glass plate (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Draper's Laboratory Equipment, undated; cuid14569; Glass plate (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Draper's Laboratory Equipment, undated; cuid14570; Glass plate (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14571; Glass plate (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14572; Glass plate (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14573; Glass plate (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14574; Glass plate (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14575; Glass plate (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14579; Glass plate negative (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Telescope at Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14576; Glass plate negative (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Heliostat at Draper's Hastings-on-Hudson Observatory, undated; cuid14577; Glass plate negative (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Machinery, undated; cuid14578; Glass plate negative (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Train Station, undated; cuid14580; Glass plate negative (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Person in Draper's Laboratory, undated; cuid14581; Glass plate negative (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Series V. D.W. Hering X-Ray Images, circa 1885-1910s
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14543; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14544; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14545; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14546; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14547; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14548; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - X-Ray, undated; cuid14549; Glass plate (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Series VI. NYU Campus, Students, and Related Images, 1890s, 1913, 1926, undated
  - NYU Campus Model, 1890s; cuid14585; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14587; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14588; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14589; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NYU Campus Model, 1890s; cuid14594; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14595; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14596; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14597; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - NYU Campus, 1890s; cuid14598; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14582; Glass plate negative (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14583; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14584; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14590; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14591; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14592; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - NYU Exhibit at World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago -- by C.L. Bristol, 1893; cuid14593; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - NYU Main Building, 1894; cuid14599; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - NYU Main Building, 1894; cuid14600; Glass plate (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - University Heights Biological Lab, circa 1895; cuid14610; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Students on Steps Outside Gould Memorial Library During Chapel Hour, from page 88 of the 1914 Violet, 1913; cuid14612; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Class Day at the Heights Campus, circa 1913; cuid14613; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Chemistry Lab, from page 228 of the 1914 Violet, 1913; cuid14614; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - NYU Ironwork -- Guggenheim Lab, 9 July 1926; cuid14618; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Group of Men, undated; cuid14601; Glass plate (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- New Central Bridge, Haven River and 155th, undated; cuid14602; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- Valley at Harlem, undated; cuid14603; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- Railroad, Station, and Street Scene, undated; cuid14604; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- New Government Ship Canal Connecting Harlem and Hudson Rivers, circa 1895; cuid14605; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- Bridge Over River with Kessell's Manhattan Par(lor?) and Lion Brewery, undated; cuid14606; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- Bridge Construction with Workmen in Foreground, undated; cuid14607; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Heights Neighborhood -- Bridge / Road with Horse and Carriage in Foreground, undated; cuid14608; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Class in Surveying -- University Heights Grounds -- Shadow of Cameraman in Foreground, circa 1895; cuid14609; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Class in Surveying Engineering, undated; cuid14611; Glass plate (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14615; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14616; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14617; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14619; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14620; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14621; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14622; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14623; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14624; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14625; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14626; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14627; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14628; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14629; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Student Life, undated; cuid14630; Glass plate (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Portraits of a Woman, undated; cuid14631; Glass plate (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Series VII. Lecture Presentation Support Images, 1863-1897, undated
  - Moon, 3 August 1863; cuid14700; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Moon, 3 August 1863; cuid14705; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Moon, 3 August 1863; cuid14704; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Moon, 4 August 1863; cuid14698; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Moon, 27 August 1863; cuid14694; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Moon, 27 August 1863; cuid14706; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Moon, 28 August 1863; cuid14697; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Moon, 30 August 1863; cuid14702; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Moon, 30 August 1863; cuid14708; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - Moon, 30 August 1863; cuid14703; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Moon, 2 September 1863; cuid14714; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - Moon, 12 June 1864; cuid14716; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - Moon, 15 June 1864; cuid14701; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Moon, 16 June 1864; cuid14713; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - Moon, 19 June 1864; cuid14699; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Moon, 21 June 1864; cuid14712; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - Moon, 22 June 1864; cuid14715; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - Moon, 22 June 1864; cuid14717; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - Moon, 22 June 1864; cuid14718; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - Moon, 22 June 1864; cuid14719; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - Moon, 23 June 1864; cuid14720; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - Moon, 25 June 1864; cuid14723; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - Moon, 25 August 1864; cuid14711; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - Moon, August 1864; cuid14721; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - Moon, August-September 1864; cuid14722; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - Moon, August-September 1864; cuid14726; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - Moon, 14 September 1864; cuid14724; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 93)
  - Moon, 16 September 1864; cuid14695; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Moon, 17 September 1864; cuid14725; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 94)
  - Moon, 17 September 1864; cuid14727; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - Moon, 13 October 1864; cuid14709; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - Moon, 15 October 1864; cuid14696; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Moon, 15 October 1864; cuid14710; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - Moon, 18 October 1864; cuid14707; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Colored Spectra of a Star, 18 February 1869; cuid14729; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 98)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, circa 1870; cuid14688; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, circa 1870; cuid14689; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Laboratory Spectrum of CuNO5, circa 1870; cuid14690; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Laboratory Spectrum of Tin and Mercury, circa 1870; cuid14691; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Laboratory Spectrum of Magnesium, circa 1870; cuid14692; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Laboratory Spectrum of Platinum, circa 1870; cuid14693; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Solar Spectra, 1873; cuid14755; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 124)
  - Solar Spectra, 1873; cuid14756; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 125)
  - Solar Spectra, 1873; cuid14757; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 126)
  - Solar Spectra, 1873; cuid14758; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 127)
  - Nova Aurigae, 1890-1891; cuid14775; Lantern slide (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - AZ 29 -- Nova Normae, 1893; cuid14782; Lantern slide (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - AZ 30 -- Nova Normae, 1893-1899; cuid14781; Lantern slide (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Radiograph of Frog with Piece of Lead in Thorax, 1896; cuid14667; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Lead Pencil, Steel Calipers, Fountain Pen, 1896; cuid14668; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Clam Shell, 1896; cuid14669; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Disc of Lead, 1896; cuid14670; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Radiograph of Steel Gauge in Morocco Case and Metal Badge in Round Wooden Box, 1896; cuid14671; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Radiograph of Steel Gauge in Morocco Case and Other Objects, 1896; cuid14672; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Radiograph of Knife, Small Carbon Pencil, Chalk, Crayon, and Dropper, 1896; cuid14673; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Photographic Action of Radium A Over Circular Gauge and Radium B Over Rectangular Gague, 1900; cuid14674; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Radiograph of Steel Gauge in Morocco Case and Other Objects, 1896; cuid14675; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Radiograph of Steel Calipers Enclosed in Wooden Box and Keys Outside of Box, 1896; cuid14677; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Taking Radiograph at NYU, 1896; cuid14680; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Pine Hill Highway Bridge, 1897; cuid14656; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Moon -- Possible Copy of Draper's Original, 15 June, undated; cuid14634; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Moon -- Possible Copy of Draper's Original, 22 June, undated; cuid14637; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Moon, undated; cuid14635; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Moon, undated; cuid14636; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Colored Spectra, undated; cuid14728; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 97)
  - Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14632; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14633; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Mars-Schiaparelli, undated; cuid14638; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Parallax, undated; cuid14639; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Coincidence of the Spectrum of Iron, undated; cuid14640; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Astronomy, undated; cuid14641; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Telescope, undated; cuid14642; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Telescope, undated; cuid14643; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Living Room, undated; cuid14644; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Harvard College Observatory Arequipa Station, undated; cuid14645; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Harvard College Observatory Arequipa Station, undated; cuid14646; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Hot Springs, Isle Ngau, undated; cuid14647; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Jungle Landscape, undated; cuid14648; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Siberian Landscape, undated; cuid14649; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Cityscape, undated; cuid14650; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Cityscape, undated; cuid14651; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Cityscape, undated; cuid14652; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Landscape, undated; cuid14653; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Mountain Range, undated; cuid14654; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Bridge, undated; cuid14655; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Johnstown Ruins-Smoking Buildings, undated; cuid14657; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Johnstown Ruins -- Houses, undated; cuid14658; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Johnstown Ruins -- Ottenad Furniture at Broadway and Soulard, undated; cuid14659; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Johnstown Ruins -- Fourth Street and Choteau Avenue, undated; cuid14660; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Niagara Falls -- American Side, undated; cuid14661; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Covered Walkway, undated; cuid14662; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Ideal Geological Landcape -- 5 Forest of Coal Period, undated; cuid14663; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Insect Specimens, undated; cuid14664; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Nerves, undated; cuid14665; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Room's Reflection on a Sphere, undated; cuid14666; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Radiograph of Two Sheets of Strip Lead, undated; cuid14676; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Radiograph of Six Month Old Child, undated; cuid14678; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Radiograph of a Leg, undated; cuid14679; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - X-ray Outfit at NYU, undated; cuid14681; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14682; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14683; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14684; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14685; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14686; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Early Solar Spectrum, undated; cuid14687; Lantern slide (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Sun, undated; cuid14730; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 99)
  - Sun, undated; cuid14731; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 100)
  - Sun, undated; cuid14732; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 101)
  - Sun, undated; cuid14733; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 102)
  - Solar Disk, undated; cuid14734; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 103)
  - Solar Disk, undated; cuid14735; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 104)
  - Moon, undated; cuid14737; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 106)
  - Solar Disk, undated; cuid14738; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 107)
  - Solar Disk D.T.G., undated; cuid14739; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 108)
  - Solar Disk, undated; cuid14740; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 109)
  - Solar Disk, undated; cuid14741; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 110)
  - Solar Disk, undated; cuid14742; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 111)
  - Solar Image, undated; cuid14743; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 112)
  - "Painted" Spectrum, undated; cuid14744; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 113)
  - Empty Slide, undated; cuid14745; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 114)
  - "Painted" Spectra, undated; cuid14746; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 115)
  - "Painted" Spectra, undated; cuid14747; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 116)
  - "Painted" Spectra, undated; cuid14748; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 117)
  - Sunspots, undated; cuid14749; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 118)
  - Sunspots, undated; cuid14750; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 119)
  - Pair of Optical Slits, undated; cuid14751; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 120)
  - Pair of Optical Slits, undated; cuid14752; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 121)
  - Wavelength Scale, undated; cuid14753; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 122)
  - Mask with Set of Slits, undated; cuid14754; Lantern slide (Box 32, Folder 123)
  - James Prescott Joule Portrait, undated; cuid14759; Lantern slide (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - James Prescott Joule's Early Apparatus, undated; cuid14760; Lantern slide (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - James Prescott Joule's Later Apparatus, undated; cuid14761; Lantern slide (Box 33, Folder 3)